Augusta Heyder, Colorist
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Augusta Heyder, Colorist
2.1.2.3
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1362
- Augusta Heyder, Colorist, 2.1.2.3
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1362)
  Box 1363
- Augusta Heyder, Colorist, 2.1.2.3
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Himalayan Mountains, circa 1918-1920s; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sailing ship, circa 1918-1920s; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sunset, circa 1918-1920s; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sunset, circa 1918-1920s; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sunset, circa 1918-1920s; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Sunset, circa 1918-1920s; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Camel skeleton, circa 1918-1920s; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Camel skeleton, circa 1918-1920s; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Camel skeleton, circa 1918-1920s; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Camel skeleton, circa 1918-1920s; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Flowers, circa 1918-1920s; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Flowers, circa 1918-1920s; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Asters, circa 1918-1920s; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Spirea, circa 1918-1920s; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Easter lily, circa 1918-1920s; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Jungle plant with high leaves like a begonia, Malay, circa 1918-1920s; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Aviator, circa 1918-1920s; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Man with wig, circa 1918-1920s; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  - Two gentlemen wearing hats, circa 1918-1920s; 38; 3x4 color (Box 1363)
  Box 1364
- Augusta Heyder, Colorist, 2.1.2.3
  - Bearded man with hat, circa 1918-1920s; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Elderly man with beard, circa 1918-1920s; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Man with prayer beads, circa 1918-1920s; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Tibetan[?] priest, circa 1918-1920s; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Unidentified panorama, circa 1918-1920s; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Man holds horse as man dismounts, other man in horse drawn carriage, Burma[?], circa 1918-1920s; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Man on horse, circa 1918-1920s; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Man on Elephant, circa 1918-1920s; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Unidentified estate, circa 1918-1920s; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - People paddling long boat, circa 1918-1920s; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Two people placing rocks in a pit, Malaya[?], circa 1918-1920s; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Cows, circa 1918-1920s; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Dog, circa 1918-1920s; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Sheep, circa 1918-1920s; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Sheep, circa 1918-1920s; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Trees, circa 1918-1920s; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Trees, cattle in foreground, circa 1918-1920s; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Two airplanes in flight, circa 1918-1920s; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1364)
  - Naked baby, circa 1918-1920s; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1364)